你哋見到約翰？
Guess I'll
have to kill you
Guess I've seen
something that I wasn't supposed to see
I'm thinking it
was that sweetlooking blonde boy
I saw in
Dusseldorf a year ago
Because I've
seen Johann
this is how
it ends up
That's how it
works with you
It was dark and
raining when I heard those three gunshots
I was there alone
and got scared so I ran away
At the time I was
pretty certain it was Tenma who'd been shot dead
But the next day
there was this big article in the newspaper
Saying that a man named Junkers had been found dead in the same location
And that he'd
been shot three times
So then that boy
did it didn't he？
Might want to
rethink pulling that trigger
If you kill me
you'll never get
what you really want
That photograph
you've been looking for
The one of
Johan as a young boy
Let me tell you
what will happen if you do decide to kill me
If I die
I've arranged for
that photo you want so much
To be delivered
directly to the BKA
If you want to
see that photograph
You need to tell
me exactly where Tenma can be found
And just what
is so funny？
Your whole
body's quivering
You talk tough
but your legs are
shaking so hard you can barely stand
You really
do amuse me
I'll tell
you where he is
So what is
Tenma up to now？
Oh，he's still
working as a doctor
But our friend
has gone underground
Where is he？
There's this
older guy in Hanover
who was the number two man in a certain organised crime family
Well
this guy's boss
kind of freaked out
and put out
a hit on him
But the job
got botched
The guy got
all shut up
but he didn't die
So Temba's at
this remote alpine estate patching him up
It's up on a
mountain near Fussen
Excuse me
but why did you
just stand there like that？
Hey， Mister
it's almost
time for lunch
Why in the world
are we eating outside？
I just thought
the weather looks
so nice this afternoon
Why not mix up
our routine and eat outside？
Well，have our
lunch out here
Didier
go ahead and
bring the plates out here
Okay
All your wounds
are healing nicely
and this fresh
air will do you good
I have to say
Doctor
If you hadn'
t been there
I doubt I
would have made it
That country
clinic was pathetic
But the masterful
skills you possess
Allowed you
to save my life
Maybe
The one bullet
just grazed your head
And the other one
went into your leg
And passed
through cleanly
Just be thankful
it didn't catch your femoral artery
To be honest
you were
quite lucky
Lucky，huh？
Right
Alrighty， guys
lunch is served
Wow
that smells good
Heckle
Surprising
isn't it？
It tastes
delicious
Heckle may look
more like a pickpocket
But he's
actually quite the chef
don't you
agree？Hey
and what in the
hell did you mean by that？
This，my
friends，is，chicken
marrango
The，key，to，the
dish，is，the，sauce
You，have，to，get
it，just，right
It's，based，on，a
recipe，from，a
threestar，French
restaurant
called，Le
Petit，Bessin
Don't，care，how
it's，made，just
how，it，tastes
A，rent，like
you，just，can't
appreciate，the
subtleties，of
fine，cuisine
You，know，this
would，taste，even
better，with，a
dash，of，soy，sauce
Soy，sauce？
Not，that，again
You，put，soy，sauce
on，everything
I，give，up
Now，this，is，dining
When you sit
down to eat
this is how
it should be
What a waste
All my life
everything I did
was to make money
But while I was
earning all those millions
I lost things
much more valuable
Both of my parents
and my only
brother disowned me
Even my wife and
son were murdered
I always wanted
to live peacefully
And dine like we'
re doing right now
Money can really
change the way people act
Allow me to share
a good example with you
Five years ago
a covert banking
organisation was formed
to facilitate the
underground funds flowing throughout Germany
What these guys
pulled off was absolutely amazing
Within days of the dirty money flowing in through shady companies
It would come out
the other side perfectly clean
係錢laundering operation？
Exactly
On top of that
this organisation
functioned in many ways like a real bank
Making loans and
investing in speculative transactions
And it grew
unbelievably fast
In five
short years
they'd
made a fortune
Hot damn
But that all
changed this year
Because the man
who'd been running the show suddenly vanished
He hasn't been
seen in months
and no one
knows where he went
Guess what
happened then？
All of it
fell apart
The entire
operation imploded
The associates
that remained started fighting over
who would get
what was left and who would be in charge
Most of them
ended up killing each other
The entire
operation disappeared
If only they'd
been sensible
And talked things
out while sharing a fine dinner
So
你諗嗰個係殺人案，定係佢跑咗？
Keep up，Doc
我講係個頭髮蓬鬆嘅人，佢消失咗
所以，係被綁架、殺死，定係咩啊？
噢，唔係，我好確定佢仲係活著
其實佢可能係冒充學生，喺某處
學生？
That's right
I forgot
to tell you
I left out
something important
According
to my sources
the guy
who created
that money laundering organisation five years ago
was just a kid
15 years old
15 years old？
Your sources
must be nuts
No way a kid
could pull off something like that
But it's true
this kid did it
It's as if he was
conducting his own experiment
To see how
adults deal with money
As though he were
a child playing around with a line of ants
Where was
all this？
Do you know where
this covert banking operation was based？
The organisation
was headquartered in Dusseldorf
But the kid at
the top was constantly on the move
He controlled the
entire operation from wherever he was
You know？
And did anybody
figure out the last place that he was seen？
Before he
disappeared？
That's all the
details I know
But I heard right
after their young boss went missing
All of his money
hungry underlings went rushing to Munich
To Munich，eh？
Hey，Doc
why the long face？
What's going on？
I know
let's invite that
man down the hill up here for lunch
Sure，why not？
That's a good idea
Sorry，Doctor
but that man'
s my bodyguard
He needs to
stay down there
But haven't you
been officially declared dead already？
You still think there are people out there who wanna do you harm？
Are you planning
to live the rest of your life in fear？
Hiding behind
a bodyguard？
Helmut has been
with me for a very long time indeed
Go ahead， son
Go and get Helmut
So that's his name
He wouldn't
talk to me at all
I bet
Go and tell him
that his duties as my bodyguard are over
He's the only one
left who's like family to me
Ask him to join us
Have him come here so we can discuss our future at this table
Okay
Mr， Helmut
lunch time
They want you to
come up and join us
Tim is right up
there in the mountain villa
You do want
to kill him
don't you？
Is something
the matter？
That was a security breach signal from Helmut
Unfortunately
I think he's
already dead
Wait
someone's
coming after ya？
There's no telling
but
I'd say someone's
heading up here even as we speak
Mr， Helmut Czar
Go tell him
You have to tell
him to run away
Hurry，go and
tell Tenma now
Tell him，damn it
Lady
I said go tell him
But your leg
you've been shot
Don't
worry about me
go
Hang on
who's
shooting at us？
Did…
did you get him？
I'm not sure
but now's your
chance to run for it
get going
But I can't go
You're out
here in the open
I can't help you
Listen
I can handle this
just go
No，you can't
We have to
go and hide
quick
Well…
looks like
I was wrong
She didn't want
to kill Temma after all
You gonna
be alright
ma'am？
I'll be fine
but I think
he's already heading up the hill on his way to the villa
Not a chance
I would've
seen him from here
There's really only one path to get all the way up to that house
What are you
talking about？
I've explored
this whole mountain
and this path is
the only way up there
All the other
paths lead to cliffs no one can climb
So then if we
guard this trail
there's no other way Roberto will be able to get far enough up the mountain to get to the villa
You mean you
know this guy？
I know
him too well
Roberto's
after Tenma
he wants
to kill him
You know Tenma？
So who are you
ma'am？
Are you a
friend of his？
What you
laughing about，Ma'am？
Don't make me
sound so old
stop calling me Ma'am
Now get
outta here，kid
You get up
there and tell Tenma
Tell him to
run away quick
But…Ma'am
I mean lady
you're bleeding
I'll be alright
you just get up
there and warn him
But your leg
looks like it's bleeding a lot
Tenma must have
heard those gunshots
I bet he's headed
down here to take care of that guy
But that'
s not good
Roberta wants Tenma to come down here and try to save us
so he can kill him
Don't you
see it's a trap
and we're the
bait to bring him here？
But what can we do
Ma'am？
If we try to make
a run for it with your leg
you might
bleed to death
Stop calling me Ma'am
what did I
tell you？
So just what are
you to Tenma anyway？
I'm his friend
what about you
Ma'am，I mean Lady？
Aren't you a
friend of Tenma's too？
You must be
cause even though
you're hurt really bad
you're still
trying to save him
I'm not
trying to be nosy
but
You like Tenma
don't you？
Are you his
girlfriend？
You just keep
watching that side
Do you like Tenma？
Yeah，I like
him a whole lot
What exactly do
you like about him？
Lots of things
What do you
like about him？
I know you
're there
Crawl around
all you want
But you'd be
pretty stupid to shoot me again
I already told you
If I die
that picture of
Johann as a child
That you want so badly will automatically be sent straight to the VKA
I mean it
this is your
last warning
If you ever want
to see that photo
then you'd better
get the hell outta here right now
So that photo you'
ve got is something you really want？
It's a lie
and it
might not work
He's too smart to
fall for such a trick
Lady，are you
feeling alright？
I'm starting to fade
I've lost a
lot of blood
Now go
well，get
out of here
save yourself
I can't
just leave you
Tenma's on his way
He would've
been here by now
He's gotta
be headed here
I mean it，Look
there's no way he
would ever come to save me
Nothing but a
waste of time
Sailor
where are you？
Tenma，我喺度
Just stay there
我嚟到接你，Didier
Don't move
If you try
to come get us
there's a man
here that's going to shoot you
That's why he
's come here
Tenma，to kill you
Wait
I know that voice
but it can't be…
Tenma
this lady's a
friend of yours
She's been shot
and she's bleeding a lot
It's Ava
You can't die now
not when I'
m so close
I'm handing you
over to the police
Kenzo
so you can rot in
jail for the rest of your life
You hear me？
You've got decades of suffering ahead of you
I want every
waking moment to hurt for dumping me
Stop shouting
you're
straining yourself
Hey，Didier
just tell me if
you can hear me
okay？
Can you tell
where the shooter is？
No，I don't know
I've got no
clue where he is
or even if he'
s still here
Stop
yelling to him
I need Tenma alive
Hang in there
he's
getting close
He's not coming
Tieda
you're wrong
He would never
come to my rescue
It's all
over for me
Don't die， please
Why would he ever
wanna rescue me？
天色好
What's all this？
Why'd you bring me out here？ It's time for lunch
Your leg has been
healing up nicely
And I thought you'd enjoy eating lunch outside in this beautiful sunshine
You're a
lucky woman
you know
What do you
mean lucky？
Just that
The guy who shot
you was a real pro
He knew what
he was doing
He understood how difficult it would be for him to infiltrate this mountain villa
There's only one
path to get up here
And there are
security cameras everywhere
He also knew this
villa would be guarded by experienced men
So it would be
like he was attacking an alpine fortress
That was the
reason he used you
Hold on
what do you
mean he used me？
It's simple
He must have
figured that a pretty woman
making an
unexpected visit
would have a much better chance of getting all the way up here than he would
But when you
betrayed him
his whole
plan was sunk
He had no plan B
there were no
other options for him
So he got out of
here quick and cut his losses
So then
he got away
That's right
We searched the
whole mountain
This here's a
special dish
It's called
chicken morango
I tried to
recreate the recipe
but I can't
guarantee it'll be any good
You know there's
another way you were very lucky
You were lucky to
have a great doctor like Doctor Tenma treating you
So is Tenma
still here？
No
he already left
Where to？
Think he said
something about going to Munich
Munich，eh？
Alright
let's see if you
and I can enjoy this chicken
I got a feeling
you're like me
I bet it's been a
long time since you sat down
and enjoyed a
meal in peace